dango dango dango dango dango daikazoku
Dango, dango, dango, dango, a big dango family.
yanchana yaki dango yasashii an dango
A mischievous roasted dango, a kind sweet bean dango,
minna minna awasete hyaku nin kazoku
gather them all up and it's a family of a hundred.
aka-chan dango wa itsumo shiawase no naka de
A baby dango is always cradled in happiness.
toshiyori dango wa me wo hosometeru
An old dango gazes with squinty eyes.
nakayoshi dango te wo tsunagi ookina marui wa ni naru yo
The dango friends will all hold hands and form a big circle.
machi wo tsukuri dango boshi no ue minna de waraiau yo
They'll found a village on a dango planet and all smile together.
usagi mo sora de te wo futtemiteru dekkai otsuki-sama
The rabbits are waving their hands from the big moon.
ureshii koto kanashii koto mo zenbu marumete
Roll up all the happy and sad things...